going to go over the materials before we
start starting with the paints these are
winter and Newton Winton o color so
these are the student grade so they're
not as good quality as the
artists the artist o color okay um if
you're on a budget these are like three
times
cheaper so I'll be using the titanium
white cium yellow cabum orange cabum red
permanent lizin dark seen purple french
H Marine curent green Ivory
black and burnt
tumber I'll put a list of these Paints
in the
description as for
brushes be using these
Rosemary uh braa long flat
brushes medium Windsor Newton refined
Lin seed
oil
canvas I like to use
these canvas pants take up less
space this
one is if you live in the the UK
Jackson's 12x 16 It's a cotton
duck outside the
UK we've got the um B RTI 30 *
40 or say Frederick's 12 by
16 all right so those are the materials
that we're going to be using